[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the most distinctive feature of one of the largest marine creatures, which is also known to be the best diver - the sperm whale?", "correct_answer": "Its enormous head", "incorrect_answers": ["Its huge vivid eyes", "Its extremely long tail", "The unique curvatures of its fins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This tiny frog is the smallest amphibian in the world.", "correct_answer": "Brazilian Gold Frog", "incorrect_answers": ["Monte Iberia Eleuth", "Rana Minuscula", "Small Frog"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal is the largest macropod and one of Australias heraldic animals?", "correct_answer": "Red kangaroo", "incorrect_answers": ["Pademelon", "Grey kangaroo", "Quokka"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Kurt Waldheims Nazi past was revealed as he ran for president of this country, but he still won.", "correct_answer": "Austria", "incorrect_answers": ["Germany", "Canada", "Sweden"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which 1985 comedy film starred Tom Hanks, Jim Belushi and Lori Singer?", "correct_answer": "The Man With One Red Shoe", "incorrect_answers": ["The Woman In Red", "The Masque of the Red Death", "Reds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which was the first music album to sell at least 20 million units?", "correct_answer": "Led Zeppelin - Led Zeppelin IV", "incorrect_answers": ["Pink Floyd - The Wall", "Billy Joel - Greatest HitsVolumes I and II", "AC/DC - Back in Black"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Brooke Shields starred as Sue-Ellen in Dont Tell Mom the Babysitters Dead.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of birds are the villains in Alfred Hitchcocks 1963 movie The Birds?", "correct_answer": "Seagulls and crows", "incorrect_answers": ["Sparrows and robins", "Parrots and canaries", "Falcons and hawks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This planet is slightly smaller than Earth and its closest neighbor (excluding the Moon).", "correct_answer": "Venus", "incorrect_answers": ["Uranus", "Mars", "Saturn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This astral body, known as Earths only natural satellite, is the subject of study selenology.", "correct_answer": "Moon", "incorrect_answers": ["Sun", "Venus", "Jupiter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress won the Razzie Award for Worst Actress for her performance in the 1980 movie The Blue Lagoon?", "correct_answer": "Brooke Shields", "incorrect_answers": ["Farrah Fawcett", "Olivia Newton-John", "Faye Dunaway"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rachel McAdams (Claire Cleary) actually took a class on sailing when she was told that her character would in fact be sailing in the movie Wedding Crashers.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]